<resources>
    <string name="app_name">dataCollect</string>
    <string-array name="country_names">

        <item>Afghanistan</item>
        <item>Armenia</item>
        <item>Azerbaijan</item>
        <item>Bahrain</item>
        <item>Bangladesh</item>
        <item>Bhutan</item>
        <item>Bolivia</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>Croatia</item>
        <item>Denmark</item>
        <item>Finland</item>
        <item>Greenland</item>
        <item>India</item>
        <item>Pakistan</item>
        <item>Nepal</item>
        <item>London</item>
        <item>Malaysia</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="text2">This is second activity</string>
    <string-array name="country_details">

        <item>Afghanistan,[c] officially the Islamic Emirate of Afghanistan,[d] is a landlocked country
            located at the crossroads of Central Asia and South Asia. Referred to as the Heart of Asia,[22]
            it is bordered by Pakistan to the east and south,[e] Iran to the west, Turkmenistan to the northwest,
            Uzbekistan to the north, Tajikistan to the northeast, and China to the northeast and east. Occupying
            652,864 square kilometers (252,072 sq mi) of land, the country is predominantly mountainous with plains
            in the north and the southwest, which are separated by the Hindu Kush mountain range. As of 2021, its
            population is 40.2 million[6] (officially estimated to be 32.9 million[23]), composed mostly of ethnic
            Pashtuns, Tajiks, Hazaras, and Uzbeks. Kabul is the country\'s largest city and serves as its capital.
            Human habitation in Afghanistan dates back to the Middle Paleolithic era, and the country\'s strategic
            location along the historic Silk Road has led it to being described, picturesquely, as the ‘roundabout
            of the ancient world’.[24] Popularly referred to as the graveyard of empires,[25] the land has historically
            been home to various peoples and has witnessed numerous military campaigns, including those by the Persians,
            Alexander the Great, the Maurya Empire, Arab Muslims, the Mongols, the British, the Soviet Union, and most
            recently by an American-led coalition. Afghanistan also served as the source from which the Greco-Bactrians
            and the Mughals, among others, rose to form major empires.[26] The various conquests and periods in both the
            Iranian and Indian cultural spheres[27][28] made the area a center for Zoroastrianism, Buddhism, Hinduism,
            and later Islam throughout history.[29]
            The modern state of Afghanistan began with the Durrani dynasty in the 18th century,with the Durrani Afghan
            Empire being formed by Ahmad Shah Durrani. The Durrani Empire led conquests in which, at its peak, encompassed
            land that spanned from eastern Iran to northern India.[30][31] Following its decline and the death of Ahmad
            Shah Durrani, and Timur Shah, it was divided into multiple smaller independent kingdoms, including but not
            limited to: Herat, Kandahar and Kabul. Afghanistan would be reunited in the 19th century after 70 years of
            civil war from 1793-1863, with wars of unification led by Dost Mohammad Khan, where he conquered the independent
            principalities in Afghanistan. Dost Mohammad died in 1863, weeks after his last campaign to unite Afghanistan,
            and as a result, threw Afghanistan back into civil war with his successors. During this time, Afghanistan became
            a buffer state in the Great Game between the British Empire (in British-ruled India) and the Russian Empire.
            From India, the British attempted to subjugate Afghanistan but were repelled in the First Anglo-Afghan War.
            However, the Second Anglo-Afghan War saw a British victory and the successful establishment of British political.
        </item>
        <item>Armenia is a nation, and former Soviet republic, in the mountainous Caucasus region between Asia and Europe</item>
        <item>Azerbaijan, the nation and former Soviet republic, is bounded by the Caspian Sea and Caucasus Mountains, which span Asia and Europe.</item>
        <item>Bahrain, officially the Kingdom of Bahrain, is an island country in Western Asia.</item>
        <item>Bangladesh, to the east of India on the Bay of Bengal, is a South Asian country marked by lush greenery and many waterways.</item>
        <item>Bhutan officially the Kingdom of Bhutan, is a landlocked country in South Asia.</item>
        <item>Bolivia is a country in central South America, with a varied terrain spanning Andes Mountains, the Atacama Desert and Amazon Basin rainforest</item>
        <item>China, officially the Peoples Republic of China, is a country in East Asia.</item>
        <item>Croatia, officially the Republic of Croatia, is a country at the crossroads of Central and Southeast Europe.</item>
        <item>Denmark is a Scandinavian country comprising the Jutland Peninsula and numerous islands</item>
        <item>Finland is a Northern European nation bordering Sweden, Norway and Russia.</item>
        <item>Greenland is an island country in North America that is part of the Kingdom of Denmark.</item>
        <item>India, officially the Republic of India, is a country in South Asia.</item>
        <item>Pakistan, officially the Islamic Republic of Pakistan (Urdu: اِسلامی جمہوریہ پاکِستان) is a country in South Asia</item>
        <item>Nepal is a multi-ethnic, multi-lingual, multi-religious and multi-cultural state, with Nepali as the official language</item>
        <item>London, the capital of England and the United Kingdom, is a 21st-century city with history stretching back to Roman times</item>
        <item>Malaysia is a Southeast Asian country occupying parts of the Malay Peninsula and the island of Borneo.</item>


    </string-array>
</resources>